Stefan Joseph

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/stefanmjoseph

E-mail: stefanj@zaonline.in Mobile: 825 993 3597

Location: Lethbridge, AB T1K 8A2

Professional Summary:

I have graduated from BYU Idaho Business and now pursuing further education in IT through Lethbridge College in Alberta. I am experienced in Cyber Security and Cloud technology. I have a passion for working with people and technology.

Skills:

- Skilled in client communication
- Effective listener and Competent Leader
- Time management & Multitasking
- Planning, Organizing, Teamwork
- Self-motivated and can work independently.

- Reconnaissance & Information Gathering
- Vulnerability Scanning
- Exploitation, Weaponization, and Delivery
- Privilege Escalation and Persistence
- Networking Configuration & Security

Accomplishments:

- Voted President of the Student Association at Lethbridge College
- Achieved a 3.9 GPA and got onto the Dean's List for two semester in the CIT Program at Lethbridge College
- Active participation in the AgENT program at Lethbridge College and obtained a certification of completion for completing the 2 Semester program.
- Served a 2-year full-time church mission away from my family in a foreign land and adapted to the culture of the people and living standards.

Work Experience:

Cattle Tech Inc - IT Technician

June 2023 – Current

- Conducted hardware installations on clients feedlots (AP's, Routers, Switches Ubiquiti & Cambium Networks) and software installations remote desktop clients (ITSuppotr247, Fusion), antivirus/endpoints (Bitdefender/Sophos)
- Monitored and managed client's network. Implemented security policy and network caps on devices (Ubiquiti)
- Learned, implemented, and managed clients firewall and proxy servers (PfSense and AdamOne).

Lethbridge College Student Association (LCSA) – President of the LCSA

May 2023 - Current

- Active advocate for the Students at Lethbridge College, built connections and developed relationships with Municipal, Provincial Leaders and other Student Leaders across Canada
- Contributed to the establishment of the ASEC organization, attended goals, leadership, and lobby conferences
- Act as the figurehead and public representative for college students.

Lethbridge College Student Association (LCSA) – Student Representative

Oct 2022 - April 2023

- Act as a medium of communication between the students at the College and the College Board
- Active contributor at Lethbridge Academic Council, the LCSA/LCFA Teaching Excellence Awards Selection Committee, the LCSA Food Bank and the Kodiak Athletics Game Day Staff
- Planned and organized multiple student's events. (Meat Draw, DND Night, Black History Month, Mental and Physical Health Wednesdays "Wellness Wednesdays")

Redherd – Recruiter – 360 Recruiter (Cyber Security Industry)

Nov 2021 - May 2022

- Job Analysis Analyzing and understanding various client job requirements to enable the creation of job descriptions that give applicants a clear understanding of the position
- Sourcing and profiling candidates Engaging with potential candidates on multiple platforms and gathering information on their work experience and skillsets
- Screening and Selection Conducting face to face interviews with candidates to identify personality traits, confirm claimed knowledge, and determine who qualifies for advancement in the job hiring process.

FH Chamberlains Silver Lakes – Assistant Head of Department

Promoted - May 2020 - May 2021

FH Chamberlains Silver Lakes – Retail Floor Sales

May 2019 – May 2021

Education:

Lethbridge College, Alberta: (Current)

Diploma of Computer Information Technology

Brigham Young University Idaho, (USA): 2017 -2021 (Graduated)

Bachelor of Business Science in Applied Business Management

Professional Development certificates

- Practical Malware Analysis & Triage (2022)
- eLearnSecurity Junior Penetration Tester
 eJPT (2021)
- TestOut Network Pro Certification (2021)
- TestOut Client Pro Certification (2021)
- TestOut PC Pro Certification (2021)
- Business and Leadership Skills (2019)
- Basic Accounting (2020)
- Business Administration (2019)